这就是我的储物柜啦
And this is my locker.
宝贝们  快躲好
Hide, girls.
噢  你好啊  玛蒂
Oh, hi, Maddie.
我很高兴看见你的感觉好多了
I'm glad you're feeling better.
什么  哦  对
What? Oh. Yeah.
好一大截了
Way better.
呃  那个  刚刚我听见两个学生
Um... Oh, wow. You know what... I hear two students
在拐角那儿试着处理一些情感问题呢
trying to work through an emotional issue around the corner.
我来了  让路
I'm coming. Make way.
心理治疗师驾到了
Therapist coming through!
鲁尼
Rooney.
你昨天怎么了
What happened to you yesterday?
我们本来约好一起吃冰淇淋的哟
We were supposed to meet for fro-yo.
但你没出现哟
You didn't show-yo.
俺就只能打包先走了哟
Had to get it to go-yo.
呃  对  你收到我的短信了吗
Uh, yeah. Didn't you get my text?
呃  收是收到了  但是“来不了  有事”
Well, yeah, but... "can't come. Got a thing."
讲得不明不白的
Is not all that informative.
你是不是长高了
Did you get taller?
不  是  也许吧
No. Yes. Maybe.
也许是你变高了
Maybe you're taller.
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
玛蒂  你看起来不一样了
Maddie, you look different.
也许是你变高了
Maybe you're taller!
好吧
Okay...
等等  刚才那下不对劲  对不
Okay, that was weird, right?
我知道不对劲长什么样  刚才那就是了
I know weird, and that was it.
但她一整天都这么不对劲
But she's been acting weird all day.
她居然今天都没有晨练
She even skipped her morning workout.
这真不是她的风格
That's so not like her.
等等  你怎么知道  她都是早上 5 点就起来晨练的
Wait, how would you know? She works out at 5:00 A.M.
- 我一直在为你教我的折返跑复试而锻炼  - 真的吗
- I was up doing the drills you taught me for my shuttle run retest. - Really?
不  我当时在熬夜看神龙小说
Nope. I was up reading a book about dragons.
- 嘿  乔伊  - 维罗
- Hey, Joey. - Willow!
哇  我以前还从没见过他跑
Wow. I've never seen him run before.
真奇怪  我见到他他都是撒丫子跑的
That's weird. I only see him run.